[
  {
    "number": 1,
    "question": "Why do mother kangaroos hate rainy days?",
    "answer": "Because then the children have to play inside."
  },
  {
    "number": 2,
    "question": "Why do hurricanes travel so fast?",
    "answer": "Because if they travelled slowly, we’d have to call them slow-i-canes."
  },
  {
    "number": 3,
    "question": "Jill: How did you find the weather on your vacation?",
    "answer": "Bill: I just went outside and there it was!"
  },
  {
    "number": 4,
    "question": "Gosh, it’s raining cats and dogs, said Fred looking out of the kitchen window.",
    "answer": "“I know,” said his mother. “I’ve just stepped in a poodle!"
  },
  {
    "number": 5,
    "question": "There’s a technical term for a sunny, warm day which follows two rainy days.",
    "answer": "It’s called Monday."
  },
  {
    "number": 6,
    "question": "What are the hottest days during summer?",
    "answer": "Sun-days"
  },
  {
    "number": 7,
    "question": "Why do tornadoes move so erratically?",
    "answer": "They are dizzy"
  },
  {
    "number": 8,
    "question": "What is the most popular game played by tornadoes?",
    "answer": "Catch my drift"
  },
  {
    "number": 9,
    "question": "What game do tornadoes like to play?",
    "answer": "Twister"
  },
  {
    "number": 10,
    "question": "Why did the tornado get arrested?",
    "answer": "For speeding, vandalism"
  },
  {
    "number": 11,
    "question": "Where is a tornado put in jail to be punished?",
    "answer": "In a high pressure cell"
  },
  {
    "number": 12,
    "question": "What did the tornado say to the car?",
    "answer": "You wanna go for a spin?"
  },
  {
    "number": 13,
    "question": "Which weather features do druggies like most?",
    "answer": "Highs"
  },
  {
    "number": 14,
    "question": "What did Santa Claus’s wife say during a thunderstorm?",
    "answer": "Come and look at the rain, dear."
  },
  {
    "number": 15,
    "question": "How did you find the weather at camp?",
    "answer": "It was easy. I just went outside – and there it was!"
  },
  {
    "number": 16,
    "question": "If six children and two dogs were under an umbrella, how come none of them got wet?",
    "answer": "Because it wasn’t raining."
  },
  {
    "number": 17,
    "question": "Why is it so wet in Great Britain?",
    "answer": "Because of all the kings and queens that reigned there."
  },
  {
    "number": 18,
    "question": "If a band plays music in a thunderstorm, who is most likely to get hit by lightning?",
    "answer": "The conductor."
  },
  {
    "number": 19,
    "question": "Who is it that everybody listens to but nobody believes?",
    "answer": "The weatherman."
  },
  {
    "number": 20,
    "question": "What did the fog say to the light rain after her vacation?",
    "answer": "I mist you."
  }
]
